export const data = [
  {
    question: "Which K-Pop idol is originally not from South Korea?",
    option1: "Wonyoung",
    option2: "Karina",
    option3: "Hanni",
    option4: "Chaewon",
    answer: 3,
    explanation: "Hanni was born in Australia with Vietnamese parents, while the other three are originally from South Korea."
  },
  {
    question: "Which food is not categorized as Western?",
    option1: "Steak",
    option2: "Sushi",
    option3: "Spaghetti",
    option4: "Pizza",
    answer: 2,
    explanation: "Sushi is from Japan, steak is from USA, and the other two are from Italy."
  },
  {
    question: "Besides HTML, what programming language that can be used as frontend?",
    option1: "React",
    option2: "PHP",
    option3: "Python",
    option4: "Java",
    answer: 1,
    explanation: "React is a programming language mainly for frontend. PHP is basically used for backend which prioritizes function. Python and Java are only for basic programming and data structures."
  },
  {
    question: "If a computer cannot be booted, what component is missing?",
    option1: "Application Software",
    option2: "Internet",
    option3: "Mouse",
    option4: "Operating System",
    answer: 4,
    explanation: "Operating System is a main component of a computer that makes it can be booted. The other three don't affect the booting capability of a computer."
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these colors that is not a primary color?",
    option1: "Red",
    option2: "Yellow",
    option3: "Green",
    option4: "Blue",
    answer: 3,
    explanation: "Green is a mixture of blue and yellow, while the other three are primary colors."
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these characters that is not a Spider-Man villain?",
    option1: "Vulture",
    option2: "Sabretooth",
    option3: "Lizard",
    option4: "Rhino",
    answer: 2,
    explanation: "Sabretooth is a Wolverine villain while the other three are Spider-Man villains."
  },
  {
    question: "What is the capital of England?",
    option1: "London",
    option2: "Manchester",
    option3: "Liverpool",
    option4: "Birmingham",
    answer: 1,
    explanation: "London is the capital of England while the other three are cities in England."
  },
  {
    question: "In games, which element pair counter each other?",
    option1: "Water and Wind",
    option2: "Fire and Ice",
    option3: "Electric and Metal",
    option4: "Light and Dark",
    answer: 4,
    explanation: "In games, light and dark are opposite elements that are also related to real life."
  },
  {
    question: "There is only one city that is fictional, what is it?",
    option1: "Wakanda",
    option2: "New York",
    option3: "Washington",
    option4: "Seoul",
    answer: 1,
    explanation: "Wakanda is a fictional African city from Marvel comics and is a home to Black Panther. Seoul is a city in South Korea, and the other two are cities in USA."
  },
  {
    question: "Which animal that has horns but not on top of its head?",
    option1: "Bull",
    option2: "Deer",
    option3: "Rhinoceros",
    option4: "Bison",
    answer: 3,
    explanation: "Rhinoceros has horns on top of their nose while the other three hava horns on top of their head"
  },
  {
    question: "Among these metal chemical elements which one is not solid in form?",
    option1: "Chromium",
    option2: "Platinum",
    option3: "Aluminium",
    option4: "Mercury",
    answer: 4,
    explanation: "Mercury is liquid in form while the other three are solid in form."
  },
  {
    question: "Which geometry shape doesn't have an edge?",
    option1: "Pyramid",
    option2: "Sphere",
    option3: "Cone",
    option4: "Cube",
    answer: 2,
    explanation: "Sphere is a geometry shape that resembles a ball. Pyramid is a square-based shape that has four triangles on each sides. Cone is a circle-based shape that has a triangle on its top. Cube is a square-based shape that has four squares on each sides and covered with a square."
  }
];